As we discussed the shadow copies deletion earlier to VSS admin, we can also delete the
shadow copy using the WMIC, so WMIC is one of the interesting thing you can we use the WMIC
a lot of time to various attacks, so the threat tactics will be placing WMIC to various attacks,
so here you can find all the options to do that, so here we have an option shadow copy
management, so if you find the query, so shadow copy delete non-interactive, so this command
is enough to remove the shadow copy from the target machine, so currently we know we do
not have any shadow copies in the target machine, so it was not removed and the description
shows an error with an initialization failure, so we do not have any kind of shadow copy
stats where the error gets thrown now, and you can do a lot of things through WMIC, even
we are going to install the ransomware inside the machine through WMIC creating a process
call, so a lot of options needs to explore in WMIC, threat tactics is heavily utilizing WMIC
to do various tasks and to do a very malicious activity against the machine, okay?
I hope we have a clearly discussed about shadow copies and shadow copies deletion, we will
continue our discussion in the next video, see you guys, bye.